Ms. Li, your schedule needs a new addition.
السيدة لي، جدولك يحتاج إلى إضافة جديدة.
Every Friday,
كل يوم جمعة،
you are required to accompany the boss on an outing.
يُطلب منك مرافقة المدير في نزهة.
That doesn't look like me at all.
هذا لا يشبهني على الإطلاق.
Your skill is getting worse.
مهاراتك تتدهور.
Looks like you have had no time for drawing
يبدو أنك لم تجد وقتاً للرسم
since you became Chairman.
منذ أن أصبحت رئيساً.
That bakery in the west district is shutting down.
سيتم إغلاق ذلك المخبز في المنطقة الغربية .
These are their last almond croissants. If you're late, you miss it.
هذه آخر قطع الكرواسون باللوز لديهم. إذا تأخرت، ستفوتك الفرصة.
Where should I sit?
أين يجب أن أجلس؟
Are we taking a cab?
هل سنستقل سيارة أجرة؟
What are you doing?
ماذا تفعل؟
I'm fastening your seat belt.
أقوم بربط حزام الأمان الخاص بك.
What kind of melodrama are you acting out?
ما نوع الدراما التي تمثلها؟
You're choking my neck.
أنت تخنقني.
Sorry.
آسف.
Sorry?
آسف؟
Do you even know how to do it?
هل تعرف حتى كيف تفعل ذلك؟
This amount of calories could power me through half a day of meetings.
هذه الكمية من السعرات الحرارية تكفيني لنصف يوم من الاجتماعات.
In that case, you're writing today's report for me.
في هذه الحالة، أنت من سيكتب تقرير اليوم نيابةً عني.
Should you
هل ينبغي عليك
review workplace etiquette again?
هل يجب مراجعة آداب العمل مرة أخرى؟
At the very least, you should thank the boss.
على الأقل، يجب أن تشكر المدير.
I can report you for workplace harassment.
بإمكاني الإبلاغ عنك بتهمة التحرش في مكان العمل.
Where are we going now?
إلى أين نحن ذاهبون الآن؟
A secret.
سرّ.
Childish.
طفولي.
You're the mature one.
أنت الشخص الناضج.
=Secret By My Name=
=سر باسمي=
(Adapted from the novel Hotpot Loves Tangyuan by Ye Yijian)
(مقتبس من رواية "هوت بوت يعشق تانغ يوان" للكاتبة يي ييجيان)
=Episode 8=
=الحلقة 8=
Do you want this?
هل تريد هذا؟
Yes.
نعم.
If you do, let's play rock-paper-scissors.
إذا فعلت ذلك، فلنلعب لعبة حجر-ورقة-مقص.
Okay.
تمام.
If you win, I'll give it to you, okay?
إذا فزت، سأعطيك إياه، حسناً؟
Come on.
تعال.
Rock, paper, scissors.
حجر، ورقة، مقص.
Alright, alright.
حسناً، حسناً.
You win.
لقد فزت.
Here you go.
ها أنت ذا.
Thank you, big sister.
شكراً لكِ يا أختي الكبرى.
You are welcome.
مرحباً بك.
Ms. Li, your negotiation skills have slipped.
يا آنسة لي، لقد تراجعت مهاراتك التفاوضية .
You can't beat a child.
لا يمكنك ضرب طفل.
Mr. Tan, on the other hand, has improved.
أما السيد تان، من ناحية أخرى، فقد تحسن.
You used to only make little rabbits.
كنتَ في السابق لا تصنع إلا الأرانب الصغيرة.
Now you have switched to abstract art.
لقد انتقلت الآن إلى الفن التجريدي.
There's something on your head.
هناك شيء ما على رأسك.
Where?
أين؟
Come on, come on.
هيا، هيا.
I'm coming.
أنا قادم.
Childish.
طفولي.
There are so many people around.
يوجد الكثير من الناس حولنا.
It's gone.
لقد اختفى.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
Sorry for the trouble.
أعتذر عن الإزعاج.
Not at all.
مُطْلَقاً.
Come on.
تعال.
Say thank you to big sister.
قولي شكراً لأختك الكبرى.
Thank you, big sister.
شكراً لكِ يا أختي الكبرى.
I'll give you my favorite fairy tale book.
سأعطيك كتابي المفضل من كتب القصص الخيالية.
Thank you.
شكرًا لك.
You're welcome.
على الرحب والسعة.
Say goodbye.
قل وداعاً.
Goodbye, big sister.
وداعاً يا أختي الكبرى.
Bye-bye.
وداعا وداعا.
- Goodbye. - Bye-bye.
- وداعاً. - مع السلامة.
Shall we go take a look over there?
هل نذهب لنلقي نظرة هناك؟
Okay.
تمام.
Alright, let's go.
حسناً، هيا بنا.
Off we go.
هيا بنا.
Dad.
أب.
♪It has been so long since I last saw you♪
♪مر وقت طويل منذ آخر مرة رأيتك فيها♪
When we were kids,
عندما كنا أطفالاً،
we loved reading fairy tales.
كنا نحب قراءة القصص الخيالية.
We even argued over it back then.
بل إننا تجادلنا حول ذلك في ذلك الوقت.
But now I only believe in expired fairy tales,
لكنني الآن لا أؤمن إلا بالخرافات البالية.
like the chemical experiment that turns a prince into a frog.
مثل التجربة الكيميائية التي تحول الأمير إلى ضفدع.
♪Yet even that cannot be fulfilled♪
♪ومع ذلك، لا يمكن تحقيق ذلك♪
I'm leaving.
سأغادر.
I'll give you a ride.
سأوصلك.
No need.
لا حاجة.
I still have somewhere to go.
لا يزال لدي مكان أذهب إليه.
Alright.
على ما يرام.
I'll be right there.
سأكون هناك حالاً.
I'm stepping out for a moment. Watch carefully. Don't leave here.
سأخرج للحظة. انتبه جيداً. لا تغادر من هنا.
Understood, Mr. Liang.
مفهوم، سيد ليانغ.
Back then, you forced my dad to take his own life.
في ذلك الوقت، أجبرت والدي على إنهاء حياته.
My mom told me
أخبرتني أمي
it only took him three days to make that decision.
لم يستغرق الأمر منه سوى ثلاثة أيام لاتخاذ هذا القرار.
Now I'll give you thirty seconds to breathe.
الآن سأمنحك ثلاثين ثانية للتنفس.
Do you think that's enough to understand what it felt like for him to wait for death?
هل تعتقد أن هذا يكفي لفهم ما كان يشعر به وهو ينتظر الموت؟
Do not rush.
لا تتعجل.
Wait until your own son, Tan Jianfei,
انتظر حتى يأتي ابنك، تان جيانفي،
personally seals the coffin for you.
يقوم شخصياً بإغلاق التابوت نيابةً عنك.
When that moment comes,
عندما تحين تلك اللحظة،
I'll dance in the red dress you despise the most.
سأرقص مرتديةً الفستان الأحمر الذي تكرهينه أكثر من غيره.
What?
ماذا؟
My mom is missing?
أمي مفقودة؟
I've already checked.
لقد تحققت بالفعل.
There's nothing on the hospital cameras.
لا يوجد شيء مسجل على كاميرات المستشفى.
It's likely that when she was taken, they deliberately avoided surveillance.
من المرجح أنهم تجنبوا المراقبة عمداً عندما تم اختطافها.
No.
لا.
Pull every single footage
استخرج كل اللقطات
one more time. I want to go through them frame by frame.
مرة أخرى. أريد أن أستعرضها إطارًا بإطار.
Ms. Li,
السيدة لي،
you look far more striking than when you were trying on wedding dresses.
تبدين أكثر جاذبية بكثير مما كنتِ عليه عندما كنتِ تجربين فساتين الزفاف.
What?
ماذا؟
Did you come here
هل أتيت إلى هنا؟
to cry injustice at me?
أن تتهمني بالظلم؟
What do you actually want?
ماذا تريد حقاً؟
Shares?
أسهم؟
Patents?
براءات الاختراع؟
Or take me to a bridal shop and make me kneel in public?
أم تأخذني إلى متجر فساتين الزفاف وتجعلني أركع أمام الناس؟
Just say it.
قلها فحسب.
How pitiful.
يا له من أمر مثير للشفقة.
Eight years ago,
قبل ثماني سنوات،
when your dad was hanging from the beam,
عندما كان والدك معلقاً من العارضة،
did you beg that old man like this too?
هل توسلت إلى ذلك الرجل العجوز بهذه الطريقة أيضاً؟
Too bad.
سيئة للغاية.
I'm only interested in living leverage now.
أنا مهتم فقط بالاستفادة من الموارد المتاحة الآن.
Tan Zuoyan, you're asking to die!
تان زويان، أنت تطلب الموت!
So eager to stage a tragic act?
هل أنت متلهفٌ جداً لارتكاب عمل مأساوي؟
Should I add
هل أضيف
some background music for you?
هل ترغب ببعض الموسيقى الخلفية؟
Let her go.
اسمح لها أن تذهب.
Mr. Tan, what are you playing at?
سيد تان، ما الذي تفعله؟
When my dad was hanging from the beam eight years ago,
عندما كان والدي معلقاً من العارضة قبل ثماني سنوات،
you didn't step up as a hero.
لم تتصرف كبطل.
Now you suddenly act like a saint.
والآن تتصرف فجأة كقديس.
Shujing,
شوجينغ،
we can...
يمكننا...
Shut up.
اسكت.
Tan Zuoyan, what do you want?
تان زويان، ماذا تريد؟
I want
أريد
Tan Zheng'en.
تان زينجين.
Any leads?
هل لديكم أي معلومات؟
Not yet.
ليس بعد.
So the old man really is with you.
إذن، الرجل العجوز معك حقاً.
How are the arrangements going
كيف تسير الترتيبات؟
for moving Tan Zheng'en?
لنقل تان تشنغ إن؟
When does the helicopter arrive?
متى ستصل المروحية؟
Everything is basically in place.
كل شيء جاهز بشكل أساسي.
The helicopter will land on the rooftop in forty minutes.
ستهبط المروحية على سطح المبنى خلال أربعين دقيقة.
But
لكن
Tan Zuoyan wants us to hand him over first.
يريد تان زويان أن نسلمه أولاً.
You actually believe that nonsense?
هل تصدق هذا الهراء حقاً؟
If your mom were in his hands,
لو كانت والدتك بين يديه،
he would've sent a live video by now.
كان سيرسل فيديو مباشرًا الآن.
Do you think he is a philanthropist?
هل تعتقد أنه فاعل خير؟
Calm your mind.
هدّئ عقلك.
Let's wait a bit longer.
لننتظر قليلاً.
Of course you're not in a hurry.
بالطبع لستَ في عجلة من أمرك.
You're afraid that once Tan Zheng'en is handed over,
أنت تخشى أنه بمجرد تسليم تان تشنغ إن،
the chairman of Tan Group will become Tan Zuoyan, right?
سيصبح رئيس مجلس إدارة مجموعة تان هو تان زويان، أليس كذلك؟
Is that how you see me?
هل هذه هي الطريقة التي تراني بها؟
I honestly don't care where Tan Zheng'en is
بصراحة، لا يهمني أين تان تشنغ إن
or who he is with.
أو مع من يكون.
I truly do not.
لا أعتقد ذلك حقاً.
But I do know this.
لكنني أعرف هذا.
If you hand him over now,
إذا سلمته الآن،
you'll be driving the final nail
ستكون أنت من يدق المسمار الأخير
into your mom's coffin.
في نعش والدتك.
Jingshu.
جينغشو.
Something about this is off.
هناك شيء ما غير طبيعي في هذا الأمر.
Tan Zuoyan keeps stalling and refuses to make the exchange face-to-face.
يستمر تان زويان في المماطلة ويرفض إجراء التبادل وجهاً لوجه.
That is suspicious.
هذا أمر مثير للريبة.
Is it possible
هل هذا ممكن
that your mom isn't in Tan Zuoyan's hands at all?
ألا تكون والدتك في يد تان زويان على الإطلاق؟
Or maybe she went missing on her own?
أو ربما اختفت من تلقاء نفسها؟
Even if there is only a one percent chance, I have to try.
حتى لو كانت نسبة الاحتمال واحد بالمئة فقط، يجب أن أحاول.
We can hand over Tan Zheng'en,
يمكننا تسليم تان زينجين،
but we must
لكن يجب علينا
see your mom first before doing so.
استشر والدتك أولاً قبل القيام بذلك.
If we give up our only leverage
إذا تخلينا عن وسيلتنا الوحيدة للتأثير
and then
وثم
still do not see her,
ما زلت لم أرها،
we'll lose the upper hand.
سنفقد زمام المبادرة.
What's your problem?
ما مشكلتك؟
You shouldn't have played that card.
كان عليك ألا تستخدم تلك الورقة.
You're making a mess of everything like that madwoman.
أنتِ تُفسدين كل شيء مثل تلك المرأة المجنونة.
At least now
على الأقل الآن
she's finally asleep.
لقد نامت أخيراً.
Exactly.
بالضبط.
It's finally quiet for a while.
أخيراً ساد الهدوء لفترة من الوقت.
Doesn't it feel a little too quiet?
ألا يبدو المكان هادئاً أكثر من اللازم؟
No way! She's gone!
مستحيل! لقد رحلت!
Alive!
على قيد الحياة!
I wanted her alive.
كنت أريدها أن تبقى على قيد الحياة.
You useless lot!
يا لكم من مجموعة عديمة الفائدة!
You couldn't even keep one madwoman under watch, huh?
ألم تستطع حتى إبقاء امرأة مجنونة واحدة تحت المراقبة؟
If you can't handle that, don't come back.
إذا لم تستطع تحمل ذلك، فلا تعد.
Too many blind spots on the cameras.
توجد نقاط عمياء كثيرة في الكاميرات.
Still no leads.
لا تزال الأمور غامضة.
Mom.
أم.
Shu… Shujing.
شو... شوجينغ.
If I lose my mother,
إذا فقدت أمي،
then I really have no home left.
إذن، لم يعد لديّ منزل حقاً.
Shujing.
شوجينغ.
I'll help you find her.
سأساعدك في العثور عليها.
I'll stay by your side too.
سأبقى بجانبك أيضاً.
In the future,
في المستقبل،
we could even have a child.
بل قد ننجب طفلاً.
You won't be without a home. We can...
لن تبقى بلا مأوى. نستطيع...
We can think of many ways.
يمكننا التفكير في طرق عديدة.
Get lost!
اغرب عن وجهي!
This is where my dad
هذا هو المكان الذي كان فيه والدي
was driven to his death by the Tan family.
دفعته عائلة تان إلى حتفه .
And now, my mom can't live in peace.
والآن، لا تستطيع أمي أن تعيش بسلام.
I'm sorry.
أنا آسف.
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪An ending that can never be undone♪
♪نهاية لا يمكن التراجع عنها♪
♪Disrupting the old rhythm, laying traps♪
♪إفساد الإيقاع القديم، ونصب الفخاخ♪
♪A board full of snares♪
♪لوح مليء بالطبول♪
♪Carving the past into every smile and word♪
♪ننقش الماضي في كل ابتسامة وكلمة♪
♪After falling, still searching for♪
♪بعد السقوط، ما زلت أبحث♪
♪The old marks♪
♪العلامات القديمة♪
♪Pages filled with attempts to hide the past♪
♪صفحات مليئة بمحاولات إخفاء الماضي♪
♪The next page♪
♪الصفحة التالية♪
♪Is turned, revealing this land of right and wrong♪
♪تتحول، كاشفةً عن هذه الأرض التي فيها الحق والباطل♪
♪A lone bird flying against the crowd♪
♪طائر وحيد يحلق عكس اتجاه الحشد♪
♪Shaking off the dust, yet still circling back♪
♪ينفض الغبار، لكنه لا يزال يعود أدراجه♪
♪Following time's hidden veins toward the next dawn♪
♪نتبع عروق الزمن الخفية نحو الفجر التالي♪
♪Besieged by the night sealed deep below♪
♪محاصرون بالليل، مختومون في الأعماق♪
♪As the mist clears, searching for light's cure♪
♪مع انقشاع الضباب، بحثًا عن علاج النور♪
♪The road is narrow, yet the way I came is not forgotten♪
♪الطريق ضيق، لكن الطريق الذي أتيت منه لم يُنسَ♪
♪The way I came♪
♪الطريقة التي أتيت بها♪